A 22 -year -old Chinese woman who suffered from a persistent cough was shocked to
learn that she had a piece of chicken bone lodged in her lung.
learn that she had a of chicken bone lodged in her lung.
A 22 -year -old Chinese woman who suffered from a persistent cough was shocked to
learn that she had a piece of chicken bone lodged in her lung.
The unnamed woman from the province of Shandong started to have coughing problems
when she was seven or eight years old.
For 14 years, she made numerous hospital visits.
However, no doctor could identify any problem.
Her uncontrollable coughing was a
For 14 years, she made numerous hospital visits.
However, no doctor could identify any problem.
Her uncontrollable coughing was a mystery.
For 14 years, she made numerous hospital visits.
However, no doctor could identify any problem.
Her uncontrollable coughing was a mystery.
Finally, the woman got a full body scan at a hospital in the city of Qingdao.
This special medical procedure revealed she had a chicken bone stuck in her lung.
Finally, the woman got a full body scan at a hospital in the city of This special
medical procedure revealed she had a chicken bone stuck in her lung.
Finally, the woman got a full body scan at a hospital in the city of Qingdao.
This special medical procedure revealed she had a chicken bone stuck in her lung.
Doctors performed surgery and removed the bone.
Doctors simple procedure went smoothly and the woman has recovered fully.
The simple procedure went smoothly and the woman has recovered fully.
Doctors performed surgery and removed the bone.
With the bone finally removed from her lung, the woman is very happy that she no
longer suffers from